http://www.engr.iupui.edu/privacy

HomePrivacy NoticePrivacy NoticePrivacy NoticeEffective: 2019-07-31ApplicabilityThis privacy notice applies only to the Purdue School of Engineering & Technology (https://et.iupui.edu) and explains our practices concerning the collection, use, and disclosure of visitor information. Visitor information collected by Purdue School of Engineering & Technology will be used only as outlined in this privacy notice.Other units at the university may collect and use visitor information in different ways. Therefore, visitors to other university websites should review the privacy notices for the particular sites they visit. Purdue School of Engineering & Technology is not responsible for the content of other websites or for the privacy practices of websites outside the scope of this notice.ChangesBecause Internet technologies continue to evolve rapidly, Purdue School of Engineering & Technology may make appropriate changes to this notice in the future. Any such changes will be consistent with our commitment to respecting visitor privacy, and will be clearly posted in a revised privacy notice.Collection and UsePassive/Automatic CollectionWhen you view pages on our site, the web server automatically collects certain technical information from your computer and about your connection.This site is hosted on Webserve, a shared web–hosting environment provided by IU’s University Information Technology Services. For more information about privacy practices related to Webserve, read the Webserve Privacy Notice Supplement.In addition to any information collected by Webserve, our server and/or site collects the following:your IP addressthe domain name from which you visit our sitethe referring websitethe date and time of visitthe duration of visityour browser typeContinued use of our website indicates consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of this information as described in this notice.Active/Manual/Voluntary CollectionOther than automatically collected technical information about your visit (described above, or cookies, described below), we may ask you to provide information voluntarily, such as through forms or other manual input—in order to make products and services available to you, to maintain and manage our relationship with you, including providing associated services or to better understand and serve your needs. This information is generally retained as long as you continue to maintain a relationship with us. Your providing this information is wholly voluntary. However, not providing the requested information (or subsequently asking that the data be removed) may affect our ability to deliver the products or service for which the information is needed. Providing the requested information indicates your consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of this information as described in this notice. Information we may actively collect could include:the email addresses of those who communicate with us via emailnameaddresstelephone numberinformation volunteered by the visitor, such as preferences, survey information and/or site registrationsInformation Used For ContactIf you supply us with your postal/mailing address:You may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events.If you do not wish to receive such mailings, or would like to be added to our "do not share" list, please let us know by:writing to us at the listed addressInformation SharingWe may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations.We do not share any personally identifiable information with other entities or organizations, except when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website.Except as described above, we will not share any information with any party for any reason.Except as provided in the Disclosure of Information section below, we do not attempt to use the technical information discussed in this section to identify individual visitors.CookiesA cookie is a small data file that is written to your hard drive that contains information about your visit to a web page. If you prefer not to receive cookies, you may configure your browser not to accept them at all, or to notify and require approval before accepting new cookies. Some web pages/sites may not function properly if the cookies are turned off, or you may have to provide the same information each time you visit those pages.In order to customize the information and services offered to you, our site uses cookies to:record user-specific information on what pages users access or visitrecord past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our siteChildrenThis site is not directed to children under 13 years of age, does not sell products or services intended for purchase by children, and does not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and teachers to be involved in children’s Internet explorations. It is particularly important for parents to guide their children when they are asked to provide personal information online.Use of Third Party ServicesThis website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses cookies (described above) to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including possibly your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google.For more information, please visit Google’s Privacy Policy.Social MediaThird-party social media sites may collect information from this site. Indiana University is not responsible for their privacy practices. This site embeds features from third party social media sites, including:Facebook (visit Facebook's privacy policy at: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)Twitter (visit Twitter's privacy policy at: https://twitter.com/en/privacy)Instagram (visit Instagram's privacy policy at: https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875)Additional Information Related to the Use of Third Party ServicesAdditionally, we may use third-party software to implement email marketing campaigns and manage other interactive marketing initiatives. This third-party software may use cookies or similar tracking technology to help manage and optimize your online experience with us. For more information about opting-out of interest-based ads, visit the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out Tool or Digital Advertising Alliance Opt-Out Tool.Updating Inaccurate InformationIn some cases, we will grant visitors the ability to update or correct inaccuracies in the information that we maintain.Visitors may correct inaccuracies in:contact information that we have on fileVisitors can have this information corrected by:sending us email at the listed addressDisclosure of InformationOther than sharing your information with other appropriate university personnel and units to ensure the quality, functionality, and security of our website, or manage your relationship with us, we will not disclose personally identifiable information about your use of the site except under the following circumstances:With your prior written (including email) consentWhen we have given you clear notice that we will disclose information that you voluntarily provideWith appropriate external parties, such as law enforcement agencies, in order to investigate and respond to suspected violations of law or university policy. Any such disclosures shall comply with all applicable laws and university policies.SecurityDue to the rapidly evolving nature of information technologies, no transmission of information over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. While Indiana University is committed to protecting user privacy, IU cannot guarantee the security of any information users transmit to university sites, and users do so at their own risk.We will comply with all applicable federal, state and local laws regarding the privacy and security of user information.Links to non-university sitesIndiana University is not responsible for the availability, content, or privacy practices of non-university sites. Non-university sites are not bound by this site privacy notice policy and may or may not have their own privacy policies.Privacy Notice ChangesFrom time to time, we may use visitor information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice.Only data collected from the time of the policy change forward will be used for these new purposes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our website periodically.Contact InformationIf you have questions or concerns about this policy, please contact us.Purdue School of Engineering & TechnologyATTN: ET Webmaster799 W. Michigan St.Indianapolis, IN 46202etwebsrv@iupui.edu317.274.2533If you feel as though this site’s privacy practices differ from the information stated, you may contact us at the listed address or phone number.If you feel that this site is not following its stated policy and communicating with the owner of this site does not resolve the matter, or if you have general questions or concerns about privacy or information technology policy at Indiana University, please contact the chief privacy officer through the University Information Policy Office, 812-855-UIPO, privacy@iu.edu.
Purdue School of Engineering & Technology social media channels
799 W. Michigan Street Indianapolis, IN 46202-5195 Phone: 317-274-2533 Fax: 317-274-4567
Request More Information Faculty & Staff Intranet
